Episode 15: Kyoto Sister School Exchange Event - Group Battle 1 -
We're starting in one minute.
Now, let's hear a few words of well-appreciated
encouragement from Iori Utahime-sensei.
Huh?!
U-Uh...
Um, some degree of injury will be unavoidable,
but, um... now and then, help
each other out... or something...
Time's up.
Hey! Gojou, you little...
Now, let the sister school exchange event...
begin!
Respect your seniors!
Ichiro?!
So stupid.
Where's Toudou?
What makes you think I would know?
Can't we all get along?
Where do you think
the cursed spirit boss is?
It was probably unleashed
halfway between both schools,
but it's not just going to sit still.
At the time we agreed upon,
we'll split up into the Megumi squad
and the Panda squad for scouting.
We'll be counting on you after that, Yuuji.
Yeah!
Where are you going?
That's small fry.
Senpai, stop!
Great! You're all here!
Come at me all together!
Scatter!
Toudou was alone.
We were right to swap Yuuji into that role.
I already knew it, but he's a monster.
Yup.
So just ignore him.
Tuna.
JUJUTSU KAISEN
Before the Exchange Event Started
Toudou will absolutely be
out to crush us straight away.
Mai might follow behind him
to come after me, too.
Toudou's a monster.
The worst possible outcome would be
that we all face him and get wiped out.
So our plan was to leave just one person,
either Panda or Megumi,
behind to occupy him, but...
Itadori, we'll leave that role to you.
We'd rather not lose anyone
who can scout out our enemies.
You don't have to beat him.
Just hold out as long as
possible and buy us time.
But you can be daring against him!
To be blunt, we weren't counting
on your abilities anyway,
so it won't affect us too
much if you have to quit.
That's mean!
Sorry, Megumi.
You wanted to face Toudou, didn't you?
No, I'm good either way.
You're super dry.
But Senpai, if I'm gonna do this,
then I'm gonna win.
Nice speed.
Seriously?
I thought I landed a good one.
I'll return the favor, first-year.
Guard like your life depends on it!
Where?
My arm's... still here?
I thought it got blown off.
If that cursed spirit
hadn't gotten in the way,
that would have been real bad.
Done already?
Now, which should I pursue?
Are you for real?
You think you can just pound
away at my head like that?!
What if you made me even
dumber than I already am?!
Don't worry.
Takada-chan said, "Men are perfect
when they're a little dumb."
Who's that?
I'm not interested in any idols.
Then how did you know she's an idol?
You know who she is, don't you?
What's your name, first-year?
Itadori Yuuji.
I see. Itadori Yuuji.
I have one question for you.
What kind of woman is your type?
Huh?
What's my type?
Why are you asking me that right now?
Don't worry about that.
I'm just appraising you.
I don't really get it, but if I had to say...
A tall woman with a big ass, I guess?
Like Jennifer Lawrence.
The new series is pretty good.
Oh?
I'm going to confess to Takada-chan.
Huh?! Don't do that!
I don't wanna have to comfort you later!
That's such a pain!
Why are you assuming she'll reject me?
I could ask you why you
think she'll say yes.
Anne Sullivan once said to Helen Keller,
"What fool thinks of defeat
before even trying?"
Inoki was the one who said that.
I'm sorry.
I'm already in love with someone.
Any chance that someone is me?
No way, man.
Come on, let's go.
I'll treat you to some ramen.
You never lost to anyone
in your hometown, huh?
Seems like we're best friends!
When you just learned my name?!
Yeah, continue straight that way.
Toudou-kun's there, though.
Not a problem.
He's the one who told us to do as we pleased.
New Shadow Style, Simple Domain:
Quick Draw!
What reflexes!
I know I hesitated, but still,
my counter didn't even scratch him!
I'm surrounded?
Wait...
Are these guys...
trying to kill me?
This is...
Itadori and I switched places?!
Hey.
I told you I'd kill you if
you interfered, didn't I?
No, you didn't.
You said you'd kill us if
we ordered you around.
Was that Itadori's...
No, it was Toudou's technique?
Same thing. Piss off!
Looks like he's retreating.
Lame.
Thank goodness!
Make sure you kill him.
That depends on Itadori.
Don't order me around.
What's with these people,
trying to kill me and then
arguing with each other?
After all, I'm not an inconsiderate man
who'd hold back against his best friend!
This is why I said to leave him be.
We're off to a rocky start.
We can't start hunting down cursed spirits
without me scouting from the air, either.
They're all such a hassle.
Hang in there, me.
You're as cute as ever today.
Take her down.
Oh, no.
Mai, Mechamaru, cover Nishimiya.
At once.
Well, we are in trouble without her.
Kamo-san, are you guys
planning to kill Itadori?
JUJUTSU KAISEN
That's strange.
It is strange.
All the Kyoto students are moving together.
Toward the area we left Yuuji in.
I think that puts everyone from Kyoto there?
You mean that's where the target is?
No, unless the second-grade
is especially cunning,
my Demon Dog would have noticed it.
They're trying to kill Itadori, aren't they?
What the hell?! I don't see why!
It's possible.
Kelp.
I didn't sense that much hostility from them,
but that was prior to Yuuji's surprise survival.
It's entirely possible that
Principal Gakuganji would order that.
Are the Kyoto students a bunch of cowards
who'd kill a person on someone else's orders?
They don't see him the same way.
You two have spent day after day with Yuuji.
We only recently learned that
he's a good person ourselves.
He's a naturally happy sort you
don't often see among sorcerers.
But the thing is...
To those who don't know
anything about Yuuji,
the vessel of Sukuna
is just an object of fear.
It wouldn't feel any different
from exorcising a curse to them.
Even normal jujutsu sorcerers
can easily blur that line.
We're turning back, Megumi.
Sorry.
What are you apologizing for, dummy?
There's no point in winning or losing
the exchange event if your friend dies.
Nobara and I will go back
to confirm that Yuuji's safe.
He's not answering his phone, either.
Toge, you keep hunting down
the cursed spirit, please.
Bonito flakes.
I know you're worried about Yuuji, too.
But if my prediction is correct,
the Kyoto students are trying
to use the chaos of the group
battle to assassinate Yuuji.
Once the group battle's over,
there won't be any assassination.
Makes sense.
Salmon.
I'm worried about Maki, too.
We won't let them kill Yuuji,
and we'll win this group battle.
Of course.
Answer on the first ring, Fushiguro!
Also, why didn't they provide us with
wireless radios or Bluetooth earbuds?!
I wouldn't want them.
They're distracting, and they startle
you when you get a call.
You can take them off during combat!
Ow...
So that's Fushiguro-kun's Nue, huh?
Electrified wings.
Looks like they'll affect
my movement for a while.
Nishimiya-chan!
Come and play!
So crass!
Not cute at all.
Kamo-san, are you guys
planning to kill Itadori?
And if I said we were?
You failed, then.
Itadori wouldn't go down in such a short time.
We have no reason to kill him.
Yes, you do.
The higher-ups and the three
major clans have plenty.
What splendid toughness!
He's actively using the landscape
to his advantage, too!
He's gone?
He's also quick to set up his next move!
And to top it off...
He has such tremendous power!
His raw strength is greater than mine,
despite his small body!
Which is why his blows are effective
with so little cursed energy!
And that makes it hard to read his movements
from the flow of cursed energy!
But the way this cursed
energy hits after a time lag...
That's just... That's just...
...wrong!
Was that Toudou?
It was.
I think I understand why you
failed to finish off Yuuji.
So why did you distance
yourself from Noritoshi?
Are you keeping your technique
a secret from your allies, too?
I'm sorry about Itadori-kun.
I know this is an excuse,
but I'm not like the others.
Still, that doesn't mean I plan to hand
over victory in this exchange event.
Recommendation
You know that sorcerers advance in rank
through a recommendation system, right?
The exchange event is often discussed among
sorcerers without connections up the chain.
Students who perform well here
are granted many chances to
advance while they're studying.
Coincidentally, the person in charge
of a student can't recommend them.
Recommendation
For example, Gojou-san couldn't
recommend Itadori-kun to be a first-grade.
I want to become independent as
quickly as possible so I can earn money.
Why?
I'm poor!
And I have two little brothers!
Are you okay?
Are you getting along well enough with Mai?
Aren't you too nice a person?
Huh? Probably...
I won't hold back, you know.
Not a problem!
That's not what I said all that for, anyway!
My friend!
That cursed energy you
blast with a time lag...
That's a bad habit of yours!
You mean Divergent Fist?
What's he on about all of a sudden?
So long as you're satisfied with that,
you'll never beat me!
If you're satisfied with
staying on that level,
you and I won't stay best friends.
Are you okay with that?!
I don't know. I don't care about that.
Are you okay with staying weak?
No, I'm not!
That's right!
My best friend!
Juju Stroll
Q: What kind of person is your type?
Someone who's stronger
than me, at the very least.
Huh? What makes you think I'll answer?
I totally can't stand a UBSSD.
Useless
Broke
Smelly
Stingy
Dead
Do you know who Sebastian Stan is?
He has a great body.
Well, you know, I like
hot guys, like most girls,
but I want someone fun to be around, too,
and it's important whether or not he can
make you feel like he's the only one for you.
Oh, gosh, how embarrassing!
Uh, you know, uh, um...
Wh-What was it?
Um...
Um, um, um...
You know, that girl who seemed nice.
The one who seemed nice.
With the notable bangs.
Come on, come on, you know! That one girl!
Nice girl, nice girl, nice girl...
Oh, Miwa?
Yeah! Her, her, her, her, her!
Episode 16:
Kyoto Sister School Exchange Event - Group Battle 2 -